

Profile

Two years of experience as a software engineer in the full development life cycle and four years as a game software tester. Able to effectively self-manage, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team. Seeking a role where I can apply my skills and meaningfully contribute to the organization while growing professionally.

Employment History

SDET II (Software Development Engineer in Test)

Experis Game Solutions

August 2022 - December 2022

Tempe, AZ

Worked as a developer in test for Age of Empires 4.

- Created a tool to simulate combat scenarios to produce game balance data
- Fixed and added functionality to a game-play bot automation tool

Test Associate III

Experis Game Solutions

November 2018 - July 2022

Tempe, AZ

Worked as a tester for The Master Chief Collection.

- Coordinated with the team to execute test plans and other self-directed testing
- Wrote bugs in Azure DevOps and verified fixes
- Wrote task reports summarizing test coverage and results
- Trained new members assigned to the same team on project processes and standards

Software Engineer II

General Dynamics Mission Systems

August 2014 - September 2016

Scottsdale, AZ

Worked on maintaining network and logging software for a satellite 3G network.

- Implemented fixes, unit tested, reviewed code, and wrote test plans for test team verification of fixed bugs
- Revised version description and installation documentation and created an installer for a subsystem used at site
- Maintained and created new tools to parse and correlate data in logs received daily from site to detect issues and monitor system health
- Evaluated and assisted with investigations for issues found by the test team

Education

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

Arizona State University

May 2014 - 3.83 GPA

Tempe, AZ

The Web Developer Bootcamp

www.udemy.com

2019

April 2023

Introduction to Databases

www.coursera.org

A course by Meta

Details

Phoenix, Arizona

623-498-9313

<u>JaronLifsey@gmail.com</u>

<u>Portfolio</u>

Skills

C++
C#

OOP Principles

Java

HTML, CSS, Type Script

Software Testing

Git

Agile

SQL / Databases

Microsoft Office

Soft Skills

Self-Directed

Communication

Critical Thinking